Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV A: New American Library, Agent - Publisher Correspondence, 1948-1961
  - Reynal & Hitchcock, 1944-1947 (Box 100, Folder 3065)
  - Paul R. Reynolds & Son, 1950-1961 (Box 100, Folder 3066)
  - Rinehart & Company, 1944-1951 (Box 100, Folder 3067)
  - Rinehart & Company, 1952-1956 (Box 100, Folder 3068)
  - Rinehart & Company, 1957-1960 (Box 100, Folder 3069)
  - Roy Publishers, 1950-1956 (Box 101, Folder 3070)
  - Misc. R Agents, 1951-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3071)
  - Misc. R Publishers, 1951-1960 (Box 101, Folder 3072)
  - St. Johns, Richard, 1960-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3073)
  - St. Martin's Press, 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3074)
  - Sanders, Sydney A.., 1950-1955 (Box 101, Folder 3075)
  - The Saturday Review, 1954-1958 (Box 101, Folder 3076)
  - Saunders, Marion, 1950-1957 (Box 101, Folder 3077)
  - S.J. Reginald Saunders & Co., 1951-1954 (Box 101, Folder 3078)
  - Schaffner, John, 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3079)
  - Bernard L. Schubert, Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 101, Folder 3080)
  - Schulberg, Ad, 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3081)
  - Scientific American, 1954-1958 (Box 101, Folder 3082)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1944-1950 (Box 101, Folder 3083)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1951-1954 (Box 101, Folder 3084)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1955-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3085)
  - Secker & Warburg, 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3086)
  - Shasta Publishers, 1949-1958 (Box 101, Folder 3087)
  - Simon & Schuster, 1945-1953 (Box 101, Folder 3088)
  - Simon & Schuster, 1954-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3089)
  - Singer, Evelyn, 1952-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3090)
  - William Sloan Associates, 1948-1960 (Box 101, Folder 3091)
  - Stevens, Alden, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 3092)
  - Misc. S Agents, 1952-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3093)
  - Misc. S Publishers, 1945-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3094)
  - Time Magazine, 1945-1960 (Box 101, Folder 3095)
  - Tomorrow, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 3096)
  - Twayne Publishers, 1951-1960 (Box 101, Folder 3097)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1951-1958 (Box 101, Folder 3098)
  - Misc. T Agents, 1953-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3099)
  - Misc. T Agents, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 3100)
  - Misc. T Publishers, 1952-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3101)
  - University of California Press, 1946-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3102)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1945-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3103)
  - University of Florida Press, 1953-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3104)
  - University of Illinois Press, 1954-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3105)
  - University of Minnesota Press, 1946-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3106)
  - University of North Carolina Press, 1946-1958 (Box 102, Folder 3107)
  - University of Oklahoma Press, 1946-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3108)
  - Misc. U Agents, 1957-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3109)
  - Misc. U Publishers, 1953-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3110)
  - Vanguard Press, 1945-1951 (Box 102, Folder 3111)
  - Vanguard Press, 1952-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3112)
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, 1945-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3113)
  - Viking Press, 1943-1950 (Box 102, Folder 3114)
  - Viking Press, 1951-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3115)
  - Misc. V Agents, 1955-1959 (Box 102, Folder 3116)
  - Misc. V Publishers, 1953-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3117)
  - Wald, Jerry, 1959-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3118)
  - Watkins, Ann, 1949-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3119)
  - The Westminster Press, 1950-1955 (Box 102, Folder 3120)
  - Whittlesey House, 1946-1950 (Box 102, Folder 3121)
  - H.W. Wilson Company, 1946-1950 (Box 102, Folder 3122)
  - Wing, Willis Kingsley, 1952-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3123)
  - The John C. Winston Co., 1946-1960 (Box 102, Folder 3124)
  - The World Publishing Co., 1945-1955 (Box 102, Folder 3125)
  - The World Publishing Co., 1956-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3126)
  - Worley Publishing Co., 1960 (Box 102, Folder 3127)
  - Writers Newsletter, 1950-1955 (Box 102, Folder 3128)
  - A..A.. Wyn, Inc., Publishers, 1950-1957 (Box 102, Folder 3129)
  - Misc. W Agents, 1950-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3130)
  - Misc. W Publishers, 1953-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3131)
  - Yale University Press, 1945-1961 (Box 102, Folder 3132)
  - Year Publications, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 3133)
  - Misc X - Y - Z Agents, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 3134)
  - Misc X - Y - Z Publishers, 1953-1959 (Box 102, Folder 3135)
- Series IV B:New American Library / Agent - Publisher Correspondence, Addendum.
  - Abingon Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3136)
  - Allen & Unwin, 1959-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3137)
  - Appleton - Century - Crofts, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3138)
  - Argonaut Books, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3139)
  - Atheneum Publishers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3140)
  - Barrie & Rockcliff, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3141)
  - Bobbs - Merrill Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3142)
  - The Bodley Head, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3143)
  - Thomas Bouregy & Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3144)
  - George Braziller, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3145)
  - Burns & Oates, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3146)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3147)
  - Chilton Company, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3148)
  - Wm. Collins Sons & Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3149)
  - Community Publishers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3150)
  - Copyrights, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3151)
  - Coward - McCann, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3152)
  - Thomas Y. Crowell, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3153)
  - Crown Publishers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3154)
  - Curtis Brown Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3155)
  - F.A. Davis Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3156)
  - The John Day Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3157)
  - Dell Publishing Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3158)
  - J.M. Dent & Sons, Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3159)
  - Andre Deutsch Limited, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3160)
  - Devin - Adair Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3161)
  - The Dial Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3162)
  - Dodd, Mead & Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3163)
  - Doubleday & Company, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3164)
  - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3165)
  - E.P. Dutton & Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3166)
  - Evans Brothers Limited, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3167)
  - Farrar, Strauss & Cudahy, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3168)
  - S. Fischer Verlag, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3169)
  - Franklin Publications, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3170)
  - Frederick Fell, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3171)
  - Bernard Geis Associates, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3172)
  - Harcourt, Brace & World, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3173)
  - Harrington House Publishers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3174)
  - Harper & Brothers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3175)
  - Harvard University Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3176)
  - William Heinemann Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3177)
  - Helicon Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3178)
  - Holt, Rinehart & Winston, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3179)
  - The Hutchinson Publishing Group, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3180)
  - International Publishers Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3181)
  - Julliard, Rene (Paris), 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3182)
  - J.B. Lippincott Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3183)
  - Literary Projects Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3184)
  - Little, Brown & Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3185)
  - Liveright Publishing, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3186)
  - London Daily Express, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3187)
  - Longmans, Green, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3188)
  - Robert B. Luce, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3189)
  - Macgibbon & Kee Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3190)
  - McGraw - Hill Book Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3191)
  - David McKay Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3192)
  - The Macmillan Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3193)
  - William Morrow & Co., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3194)
  - Nelson & Sons Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3195)
  - New American Library schedules, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3196)
  - New Directions, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3197)
  - W.W. Norton & Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3198)
  - Oracle Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3199)
  - Pan Books Limited, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3200)
  - Lawrence Pollinger Limited, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3201)
  - Clarkson N. Potter, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3202)
  - Frederick A.. Praeger, Inc., 1960 (Box 103, Folder 3203)
  - Prentice - Hall, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3204)
  - G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3205)
  - Rand, Ayn, and Nathaniel Branden, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3206)
  - Rand McNally & Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3207)
  - Random House, 1959-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3208)
  - Reynal & Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3209)
  - Paul Reynolds & Son, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3210)
  - St. Martin's Press, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3211)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3212)
  - Sheed & Ward, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3213)
  - Simon & Schuster, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3214)
  - Spencer Press, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3215)
  - Sven - Erik Berghs Forlag, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3216)
  - University of Michigan Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3217)
  - University of Missouri Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3218)
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3219)
  - Vanguard Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3220)
  - Viking Press, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3221)
  - Wald Publishing Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3222)
  - Ives Washburn, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3223)
  - The World Publishing Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3224)
  - Darryl F. Zanuck Productions, Inc., 1960 (Box 103, Folder 3225)
  - Misc. Publishers A - Z, 1945-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3226)
  - Agenzia Litteraria Internazionale, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3227)
  - American Literary Exchange, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3228)
  - Blassingame, Lurton, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3229)
  - Brandt & Brandt, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3230)
  - James Brown Associates, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3231)
  - Carnell, E.J., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3232)
  - Jacques Chambrun, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3233)
  - Columbia Pictures Corp., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3234)
  - Curtis Brown, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 3235)
  - David, Jacques, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3235.A)
  - Ann Elmo Agency, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3236)
  - Fierst, A.L., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3237)
  - Fles, Barthold, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3238)
  - Greenburger, Sanford Jerome, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3239)
  - Hale, Jeanne, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3240)
  - Halsey, Reece, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3241)
  - Hill & Wang, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3242)
  - Hinshaw & Stuhlmann, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3243)
  - Horizon Press, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3244)
  - Independent News Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3245)
  - International Literary Agency, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3246)
  - Jackinson, Alex, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 3247)
  - Herb Jaffe Associates, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3248)
  - Joseph, Nannine, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3249)
  - Harriet Kaplan - Lily Veidt, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3250)
  - King, Kenneth M., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3251)
  - Krog, Eli, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3252)
  - Lester Lewis Associates, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3253)
  - Littauer & Wilkinson, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3254)
  - The Sterling Lord Agency, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3255)
  - MCA Artists, Ltd., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3256)
  - MacCampbell, Donald, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3257)
  - Harold Matson Company, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3258)
  - Scott Meredith Literary Agency, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3259)
  - Mills, Robert P., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3260)
  - Moorepark, Howard, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3261)
  - Harold Ober Associates, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3262)
  - O'Melvey & Myers, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3263)
  - Paragon Associates, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3264)
  - Paterson, Mark, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3265)
  - Porcelain, Sidney E., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3266)
  - The Rand Corporation, 1958-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3267)
  - Rice, Virginia, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3268)
  - Rudman, Frank, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3269.A)
  - Russell & Volkening, Inc., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3269.B)
  - Strassman, Toni, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3270)
  - Wilck, Laura, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3271)
  - Winkler, Daniel M., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3272)
  - Ziv United Artists, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3273)
  - Misc. Agents, A - Z, 1959-1961 (Box 103, Folder 3274)
  - Misc. correspondence: Allen, Walter, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3275)
  - Misc. correspondence: American Book Publishers Council, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3276)
  - Misc. correspondence: American Civil Liberties Union, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3277)
  - Misc. correspondence: Bulkley, Dunton, & Co., 1944-1955 (Box 103, Folder 3278)
  - Misc. correspondence: Bulletin du Levre, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3279)
  - Misc. correspondence: Burdell, Edwin S., 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3280)
  - Misc. correspondence: Canfield Paper Co., 1950-1955 (Box 103, Folder 3281)
  - Misc. correspondence: catalog requests, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3282)
  - Misc. correspondence: The Century Ass'n, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3283)
  - Misc. correspondence: Chapman, Daniel, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3284)
  - Misc. correspondence: Cummings, J. Bradley, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3285)
  - Misc. correspondence: The Economist Diary, undated (Box 103, Folder 3286)
  - Misc. correspondence: expenses/New American Library, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3287)
  - Misc. correspondence: Finch, Pruyn and Co., 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 3288)
  - Misc. correspondence: Franklin Publications, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3289)
  - Misc. correspondence: Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3290)
  - Misc. correspondence: Great Northern Paper Company, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 3291)
  - Misc. correspondence: hardcover submissions, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3292)
  - Misc. correspondence: Harris, Robert I., 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3293)
  - Misc. correspondence: Haynes, Jim, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3294)
  - Misc. correspondence: Independent News, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3295)
  - Misc. correspondence: invitations accepted (Victor Weybright), 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3296)
  - Misc. correspondence: invitations declined (Victor Weybright), 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3297)
  - Misc. correspondence: Literary Projects Co., Sept 1959-Sept 1961, 1959-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3298)
  - Misc. correspondence: Literary Projects Co., Oct 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 3299)
  - Misc. correspondence: Literary Projects Co., status reports, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3300)
  - Misc. correspondence: Littauer & Ullman, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3301)
  - Misc. correspondence: Mentor, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3302)
  - Misc. correspondence: memos - book requests, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3303)
  - Misc. correspondence: memos - inter-office, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3304)
  - Misc. correspondence: memos - publicity, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3305)
  - Misc. correspondence: Weybright, Victor, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3306)
  - Misc. correspondence: NEL -- reports, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3307)
  - Misc. correspondence: National Book League, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3308)
  - Misc. correspondence: Peace Corps, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3309)
  - Misc. correspondence: personnel, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3310)
  - Misc. correspondence: readers' mail, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 3311)
  - Misc. correspondence: reports, 1960-1962 (Box 104, Folder 3312)
  - Misc. correspondence: Rodgers, John, M.P., 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3313)
  - Misc. correspondence: Saturday Evening Post, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3314)
  - Misc. correspondence: The Society of Authors, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3315)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions, Jan-Aug, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3316)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions, Sept-Dec, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 3317)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions, A - K, 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 3318)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions, L - Z, 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 3319)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions - hardcover interest, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3320)
  - Misc. correspondence: submissions - unauthorized A - R, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3321)
  - Misc. correspondence: suggestions, A - T, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3322)
  - Misc. correspondence: summary of commitments, undated (Box 105, Folder 3323)
  - Misc. correspondence: take-over rumors by English publishers, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3324)
  - Misc. correspondence: translators, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3325)
  - Misc. correspondence: unsolicited file, R - Z, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3326)
  - Misc. correspondence: Weybright, Victor - honorary degree from Wagner College, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3327)
  - Misc. correspondence: Wickremesinghe, C.E.L., 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3328)
  - Misc. correspondence: Writers' Conference, Wagner College, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 3329)
  - Misc. correspondence: Xerox Reproduction Services, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3330)
  - Misc. correspondence: miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3331)
- Series V: New American Library - Manuscripts
  - Manuscripts: "Act of Violence", undated (Box 106, Folder 3332)
  - Manuscripts: "The Age of Adventure" (pages 1-150), undated (Box 106, Folder 3333)
  - Manuscripts: "The Age of Adventure" (pages 151-358), undated (Box 106, Folder 3334)
  - Manuscripts: "The Age of Ideology" (pages 1-145), undated (Box 106, Folder 3335)
  - Manuscripts: "The Age of Ideology" (pages 146 - 285), undated (Box 106, Folder 3336)
  - Manuscripts: "The Age of Ideology" (pages 286 -415), undated (Box 107, Folder 3337)
  - Manuscripts: "American Folk Tales and Songs" (pages 1-153), undated (Box 107, Folder 3338)
  - Manuscripts: "American Folk Tales and Songs" (pages 154-288), undated (Box 107, Folder 3339)
  - Manuscripts: "American Folk Tales and Songs" (pages 289-388), undated (Box 107, Folder 3340)
  - Manuscripts: "American Folk Tales and Songs": music scores, undated (Box 107, Folder 3341)
  - Manuscripts: "American Folk Tales and Songs": illustration, undated (Box 107, Folder 3342)
  - Manuscripts: "Dead Sea Scrolls" (duplicate pages), undated (Box 108, Folder 3343)
  - Manuscripts: "Delay En Route" (pages 1-130), undated (Box 108, Folder 3344)
  - Manuscripts: "Delay En Route" (pages 131-249), undated (Box 108, Folder 3345)
  - Manuscripts: "A Devil in Paradise", undated (Box 108, Folder 3346)
  - Manuscripts: "Documentary History of the United States", undated (Box 108, Folder 3347)
  - Manuscripts: "The Fastest Gun in Texas" (Plenn, J.H., and C.J. LaRoche), undated (Box 108, Folder 3348)
  - Manuscripts: "Good Night Sailor", undated (Box 109, Folder 3349)
  - Manuscripts: "Good Reading" - (incomplete), bibliography, undated (Box 109, Folder 3350)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 10-165), undated (Box 109, Folder 3351)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 166-334), undated (Box 109, Folder 3352)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 335-500), undated (Box 109, Folder 3353)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 501-669), undated (Box 109, Folder 3354)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 670-850), undated (Box 109, Folder 3355)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 851-1050), undated (Box 110, Folder 3356)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 1051-1202), undated (Box 110, Folder 3357)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 1203-1378), undated (Box 110, Folder 3358)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 1379-1600), undated (Box 110, Folder 3359)
  - Manuscripts: "Handbook of World Literature" (pages 1601-1847), undated (Box 110, Folder 3360)
  - Manuscripts: "How to be a Better Member", undated (Box 111, Folder 3361)
  - Manuscripts: "How to Know Rocks and Minerals", undated (Box 111, Folder 3362)
  - Manuscripts: "How to Use Good Reading" (Townsend, Atwood A..), undated (Box 111, Folder 3363)
  - Manuscripts: "Live Without Fear" (pages 1-157), undated (Box 111, Folder 3364)
  - Manuscripts: "Live Without Fear" (pages 158-298), undated (Box 111, Folder 3365)
  - Manuscripts: "The Mentor Book of Religious Verse" (pages 1-150), undated (Box 112, Folder 3366)
  - Manuscripts: "The Mentor Book of Religious Verse" (pages 151-265), undated (Box 112, Folder 3367)
  - Manuscripts: "The Mississippi" (Mark Twain), undated (Box 112, Folder 3368)
  - Manuscripts: "Office Wife" (pages 1-140), undated (Box 112, Folder 3369)
  - Manuscripts: "Office Wife" (pages 141-273), undated (Box 112, Folder 3370)
  - Manuscripts: "Papal Encyclicals" (pages 1-148), undated (Box 112, Folder 3371)
  - Manuscripts: "Papal Encyclicals" (pages 149-319), undated (Box 112, Folder 3372)
  - Manuscripts: "Papal Encyclicals" (pages 320-479), undated (Box 113, Folder 3373)
  - Manuscripts: "The Ten Commandments", undated (Box 113, Folder 3374)
  - Manuscripts: untitled (Chapter 1: Founard's), undated (Box 113, Folder 3375)
  - Manuscripts: untitled (Chapter 1: "You no-good bastard..."), undated (Box 113, Folder 3376)
  - Manuscripts: misc. magazine articles, undated (Box 113, Folder 3377)
- ITEMS LEFT OUT: Misc.
  - American Committee on Africa, undated (Box 114, Folder 3378)
  - Balchin, Nigel, undated (Box 114, Folder 3379)
  - Brebner, William, undated (Box 114, Folder 3380)
  - Cartoon books, undated (Box 114, Folder 3381)
  - general correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 114, Folder 3382)
  - copyright registration, undated (Box 114, Folder 3383)
  - internal memos, 1958-1960 (Box 114, Folder 3384)
  - Kinsey Report, undated (Box 114, Folder 3385)
  - Love, Edmund G., "Subways are for Sleeping", undated (Box 114, Folder 3386)
  - movie book, 1950 (Box 114, Folder 3387)
  - publishers, 1947-1961 (Box 114, Folder 3388)
  - Santillana, Giorgio de, "The Age of Adventure", undated (Box 114, Folder 3389)
  - security transactions, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 3390)
  - The Society of Authors, undated (Box 114, Folder 3391)
  - Wellsprings of Life, undated (Box 114, Folder 3392)
  - misc. news clippings, undated (Box 114, Folder 3393)
- Series VI: New American Library: Paperbacks
  - Abb-Bal, undated (Box 115)
    General
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234008
  - Bal-Ber, undated (Box 116)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234016
  - Ber-Bus, undated (Box 117)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234057
  - Bus-Cal, undated (Box 118)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234024
  - Cal-Con, undated (Box 119)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234040
  - Con-Dev, undated (Box 120)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234032
  - Dev-Dun, undated (Box 121)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234065
  - Dun-Fen, undated (Box 122)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234073
  - Fen-Gal, undated (Box 123)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234081
  - Gal-Gre, undated (Box 124)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234107
  - Gre-Hef, undated (Box 125)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234115
  - Hef-Joh, undated (Box 126)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234123
  - Joh-Kyt, undated (Box 127)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234099
  - Kyt-Lyn, undated (Box 128)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234131
  - Lyn-Mer, undated (Box 129)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234149
  - Mer-New, undated (Box 130)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234164
  - New-Par, undated (Box 131)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234172
  - Par-Rod, undated (Box 132)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234180
  - Rod-She, undated (Box 133)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234198
  - She-Spi, undated (Box 134)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234206
  - Spi-Upt, undated (Box 135)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234214
  - Upt-Wal, undated (Box 136)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234248
  - Wal-Web, undated (Box 137)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234230
  - Web-Wil, undated (Box 138)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234222
  - Wil-Z, undated (Box 139)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042234156